<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  
  <!-- EN: 静巢构体 -->
  <TW_Mech_Doxa.label>Doxa</TW_Mech_Doxa.label>
  <!-- EN: 静巢构体（Doxa-0） 是机械族中最具战术深度与火力协调能力的单位之一，其原型来自蛛形掠食者，却被机械族重构为一座自律运算的泰坦级战术火力中枢。它的设计目的并非快速歼敌，而是通过持续压制、火控锁定与战场管理，逐步令敌方陷入战术瘫痪。在整支机械军团中，Doxa-0 的部署通常意味着一场区域性的决战已悄然开始。\n	  \n\n行进中的 Doxa-0 缓慢、沉重，以几近仪式感的低频节奏在地表推进。然而，一旦其进入“架炮锁定”状态，它将主动固定于地面，解锁第三身节中的火箭阵列模块，对大片区域进行持续性的穿盾性饱和打击。在此模式下，Doxa-0 彻底抛弃机动性，转而成为一座半永久性的火力节点，压制敌方任何形式的集结或推进。\n\n\n更为致命的是它的孵化系统：战斗期间，Doxa-0 会定期释放名为“裂壳蛛”的微型支援单位。这些蛛形机械虫体积小、速度快，几乎难以预测路径，但在其死亡时会引爆局部冲击波并释放爆炸，令敌人陷入混乱之中。裂壳蛛并非传统意义上的伤害单位，而是一种用于打断、防区扰乱与后排击穿的战术武器。\n\n\nDoxa-0 的“脑核”系统则为整个战场带来更深层的危机。其高频运算能力可在极短时间内完成火力分配、目标优先级调整与支援单位指引，形成一种智能化的战术网络节点。若放任其长时间部署，将可能导致整个防御线被逐一拆解，战场节奏完全落入敌手。\n\n\n静巢构体不是用于正面对抗的敌人，它是战争节奏的塑造者，是战术系统的具现。如果不能迅速加以终结，它将用缓慢却致命的步伐，一点一点将整个殖民地拖入死亡的沉寂。 -->
  <TW_Mech_Doxa.description>Doxa is among the most tactically sophisticated mechanoids. Originally based on arachnid predators, it was rebuilt into an autonomous titan-class fire control nexus. Designed not for quick elimination but for gradual paralysis through sustained suppression and battlefield management. Its deployment signals regional decisive engagements.

Doxa advances slowly with rhythmic cadence. When anchored in Artillery Lock mode, it deploys third-segment rocket arrays for continuous shield-penetrating bombardment. Sacrificing mobility, it becomes a semi-permanent firebase suppressing enemy concentrations.

Its deadliest feature: periodically releasing Shellsplitter - micro-units with erratic trajectories that explode terminally, disrupting formations. These are tactical disruptors, not direct damage dealers.

Doxa's neural core creates intelligent tactical networks through real-time fire distribution and target prioritization. Unchecked deployment risks dismantling entire defensive lines and losing battlefield initiative.

Doxa isn't a frontline fighter but a theater-level tempo controller. Failure to neutralize it promptly leads to colony's operational death.</TW_Mech_Doxa.description>
  <!-- EN: head -->
  <TW_Mech_Doxa.tools.head.label>head</TW_Mech_Doxa.tools.head.label>
  
  <!-- EN: 裂壳蛛 -->
  <TW_Mech_Shellsplitter_Spider.label>Shellsplitter</TW_Mech_Shellsplitter_Spider.label>
  <!-- EN: 裂壳蛛是静巢构体 Doxa 系列孵化系统衍生出的短程攻击单元，具备基础战斗能力与高度机动性。其外骨骼采用轻质高频震动材料，在贴身接触中可执行连续撕裂与穿刺攻击，具备压制步兵、扰乱阵型的能力。\n\n与多数小型机械族不同，裂壳蛛并非完全以牺牲为目的，而是一种“可打可爆”的前线干扰体。它们在近战接敌时具有高频斩击输出，而一旦结构临界，其核心模块会立即释放一次局部EMP冲击波与破片爆裂，干扰周围电子系统并造成范围伤害。\n\n裂壳蛛通常以集群部署，由孵化装置快速批量制造，适用于渗透破坏、区域锁控与战术自毁任务。它们没有恐惧，只有执行指令的冷酷决心——在接近、撕裂、爆散之间完成自身的战术意义。 -->
  <TW_Mech_Shellsplitter_Spider.description>Short-range assault units spawned from Doxa-series incubation systems. Lightweight exoskeletons with high-frequency vibration materials enable rapid slashing attacks effective at infantry suppression and formation disruption.

Unlike most expendable mechanoids, Shellsplitter Spiders function as "engage-and-detonate" frontline disruptors. They deliver high-frequency melee strikes until structural failure triggers localized fragmentation explosions - damaging electronics while causing area-denial effects.

Typically deployed in swarms via rapid batch production, they execute infiltration, area denial, and tactical self-destruction missions with cold determination - fulfilling tactical purpose through approach, shred, and detonation.</TW_Mech_Shellsplitter_Spider.description>
  <!-- EN: head -->
  <TW_Mech_Shellsplitter_Spider.tools.head.label>head</TW_Mech_Shellsplitter_Spider.tools.head.label>
  
</LanguageData>